If w not that many followers and they're all at work
A first viewer welcome to my drive
Welcome we're driving to San Diego
This is the kama AI Exodus
unfortunately, I'm I
Didn't get to participate in the kama caravan, which departed yesterday
You know think like six self-driving cars following each other like like Tesla
talked about with their semi trucks
That's what that's what that's what the rest of the crew got to do yesterday
but I saved another day and packed up my impact of my apartment and
Driving solo down to America's Finest City. It's the official slogan. I love it
, said, you know moving to San Diego we published the article and
Immediately we had like 10 like
organizations and individuals from San Diego just say welcome to America's Finest City and
They all share this slogan, so I'm really I'm really happy that I
Moved into a place like I feel like I've moved to any other city and I mean, I don't know
I don't think there'd be such a a
coherent Schill army for the city
Which is quite a nice thing
San Diego's really nice
I've lived in San Francisco for you know Bay Area for 23 years and grew up here and
I'm really excited to
You know test tests out how the rest of the country is
San Diego I know it's not the rest of the country, but hey, it's far enough away and it's still
California even more beautiful than
California that I know
So we have really excited for my money to go further for comma to be close to
Qualcomm and you know other sort of
hard technology
We're one of the first consumer brands, you know consumer electronics companies to you know, startup stuff to land down there
And I think the labor market is less tight in San Francisco. I don't have to pay a JavaScript engineer
$300,000
You know that can hire people of all ages if I hire someone in San Francisco over 30
And they're already there, you know, they're they're probably expecting. Yeah, like, you know 200k Plus salary
Everything's inflated. Everything's who played in San Francisco
so yeah real excited kind of just
Talking to the stream there's fortunately no viewers
But I'm gonna keep this on
Going to keep us on and as my followers take breaks and their work day
When might need followers wake up turn on their their computer in their Twitter timeline
After a late night Mountain Dew and counter strike go binge
I
Hope I hope I hope they'll watch
Oh, yeah, he's 580 destination Fresno
Definitely Fresno is definitely not America's Finest City
Hey, what's up?
You're the first one in here. We had a few people. I'm good
We had a few people come in and leave and I've just been talking to
The boy it for five minutes
Yeah, I'm driving to San Diego right now
Driving to San Diego
because comma AI my employer is moving down there and
I'm real excited. Yeah, I'm I
Have lived in the Bay Area for 23 years
and
Yeah, North Bay East Bay, you know up towards Sacramento and yeah really excited
to move to San Diego got probably about eight hours left on the drive, but open pilots driving and
Got my oh, hey, that's awesome. I
Really wanna I really want to visit sometime. Oh
Yeah, oh my oh my Indian friends come back and they're just like wow, I can't believe you know, India
And it's especially in the cities and it's chaos is still functional
but they said India is a testament to
human resilience and
Beauty so yeah, that's great
Let's see see make it a road shop
There we go, yeah, this is a highway 580
From the Bay Area going east got to go east to the highway 5 which cuts down in the middle of California?
Yeah out here. I really don't know if you ever used Windows XP
but I get I get the vibe some of these hills are as green as the
the Windows XP desktop
paper
wallpaper
This is a beautiful part of California, hey, what's up drew?
What's up
Driving San Diego
Taking the rav4 got it a pack to the brim with all my stuff and
Yeah real real real excited to land and start it and start a new chapter with comma I think San Diego will be where we
where we grow and
Suddenly you're looking around on the highway and all these Toyota's and Honda's have have eons mounted on the windshield
And half a mile keep left to stay on i-4 how much people you I don't know it
Can you I'm not sure what that means
How you doing true
I keep left to stay on i-5 80 East
That's okay, I'm happy. I'm happy that you here and watching
continue on i-5 80 East for five miles
a welcome
Oh beyond me, it's a good username Hey
Ever driving highway 580 right now
Going east it's quite beautiful out here. I love we got we got the windmills
Got the windmill
It's smooth driving out here
This is sy way. This is my second open pilot road trip in like three days. I
drove up highway 101
with only a handful of disengagement to
To Humboldt County to see my friend
very beautiful drive
people like to take their
really fast cars up highway 101
So you gotta watch out for cops are always hiding on the weekends expecting to find some like, you know
Some dude flexing his Google bucks, you know in his Lambo
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I'm running I'm running a secret good model
Which is actually
It's better around town than the freeway
But it's been working pretty well so far
I find I find it can cut this model can cut turns a little bit on the freeway
But where we're working on sort of combining
This new model technology with the production
The production land model and
Yeah, I like to when I whenever I get off the freeway
I often just like go on SSH on my phone and check out the other model and then
Cruise around her around town. It works really well
where I
Just lived in in Berkeley
Oh man this yeah, I don't know drew if you were alright, this place gives me incredible Windows XP vibes
This this part is part of 580 because you got these like rolling green hills
It's it's beautiful
And there's no yeah, there's no traffic because yeah, I agree there's no traffic this way
I I saw all the poor commuters going the other way and
whenever I see traffic, I think look I
I hope I hope that we can deliver, you know, affordable driver assistance systems to all of you
So so even if
Even if you got to deal with the traffic, you know, I hope you can at least not be angry
Hi Alex, my name is Andy
Driving to San Diego
I don't think I'll periscope for 8 hours, but
Definitely at some points along the way. Oh
Yeah. Oh, yeah
I'm sure we'll all be or I am right now Alex. I am I am
And will town in my end, well, I'm on the way toward Stockton I'm sort of in between
Dublin Pleasanton and
Stockton
but yeah, well
we'll definitely be running the AC in our cars and certainly our next Hardware product will be very resilient to
dire temperatures
You know, I am while the EON definitely has flaws I am always astounded
I'm always astounded
at
That this legal a pro 3 can drive my car
And I know that if we could rice this one together
if we could rice this one together with the with the Lego and the one plus three that
When we have a mile use the right two lanes to take the i-580 exit toward i-5 South Fresno
when we have our next product will definitely be much higher quality and we can we can we can design it to the
specs we need
Yeah, we're hopping on the five now
Use the right two heads, so don't worry we're way past that Don and done
Continue for 241 miles
Into my unreleased unreleased jailbreak
Oh, yeah. Yeah, that was the best part. You know, it was glad it wasn't all marketing speak and they went into
you know, really and
NVIDIA needs to and media needs
Needs people to show them that they're not top of the game, you know
Tesla needs to really really nailed into Nvidia that like you guys
Like screwed us around or you know couldn't couldn't do what we wanted and we did it better
and and videos really in sad state, you know, they
They're selling up but the moment you want to ship a product
With an Nvidia, you know
Video chip or you know Drive px or whatever. The flavor of the month is
They're not they're not gonna sell to you and comma had this experience. I
spoke with I went to this DIY Robo cars event in Oakland last weekend and
Spoke with a self-balancing bicycle company that also had a similarly poor experience
you know excited to use in video stuff and then realize like one they're not going to sell it to us to
You know, they they're still very like their Linux support is still really janky
you know the
If you go on like Nvidia Support Forums the often times and in a thread where something's wrong or getting a segfault or something
The support people and/or the Nvidia engineers themselves just say well can't do anything. Sorry
So to really, you know, they're still good at GPUs, right
You know, but the
Nvidia just doesn't want to sell things especially to startup companies and you know test the tensile is I'll have you know
Nvidia chips in them but I bet Tesla had even a Tesla scale
It's not just that they're Ken Vidya is only going to sell the Tesla size companies
pretty much all their customers in this
In this field and you know in autonomous driving that are trying to ship real products
are not satisfied with what Nvidia is offering so
It's a it's a sad. It's a sad story
but you know, I hope I hope Nvidia gets their wit's and
You know starts starts distributing, you know good novel products to
you know that end up in people's hands that end up in production, but
See it pretty much seems to CPUs are the only thing to really have in production right now
Five is beautiful
At least oh
Yeah, I got that good good farm smell coming in
Right
What's that video
I love that the Tesla community and you know the Tesla Tesla forums, you know, just trying to try to hack their Tesla's
I'm happy that you know that that community exists were
for Tesla owners, and it's always cool to
You know see people's analyses and visualizations of the Tesla Model
It's uh, this is quite nice
Still waiting for the first
Windows 10 on Tesla computer
I don't know if that will ever happen
I guess I'm in Tracy now
Tracy, Tracy, California
Yeah more powerful more
Reliable Aeon
and more cameras and
Probably going to get ready to depend on giraffe to
You know, let me just want to sell you one box
My thoughts on Tom a day for Tesla
Yeah, I like ya as
Drew was talking about I enjoyed the the
Chips part of it. I think they're doing great innovation there and they're you know
exceeding in terms of performance and power consumption
what they could buy on the market from Nvidia or anyone else so
I'm very I'm very happy that they shared they shared that with the world
I'm happy that they're making progress on their driving system. I think that their timelines are a little aggressive for
You know the rideshare Network though, the long-term vision is solid
Yeah
They're you know, I'm excited for them to keep keep improving the driving system
and you know, I'm sure they're aggressive timelines are in part part in part there to
In part there to make sure that you know customers are hyped and excited and think they're good in the futures near than ever
And are also for their their it lights a fire into their their engineers ass
Definitely not the first fire we all we all know that Tesla works people real hard
But
yeah, so I'm excited to see III don't believe their timelines for full self-driving, but I think that you know
It'll be here sometime
and I hope that
I'll they continue to improve autopilot
And yeah, I'm very
very Pro very pro Tesla and
the Tesla vision and mission
but
Yeah
Yeah, who knows I mean I did
I wonder if they do they have like redundancy that you know people think is required for you know level 4
level 5 stuff
It comes software ahead affairs
On par in a lot of areas like we don't since we're still dealing with a forward facing camera, we don't yet have
like auto lane change
Or
or
Navigate but so I'd say we're trailing them on on sort of the feature list
But open pilot drives better than autopilot in a lot of scenarios
So I
am and we have a driveway of a camera based driver monitoring system that they did that they don't and I think is really
important for
For for safety with with high quality level 2 systems
So yeah
I'd say we're really just trying to stay on par and if we if we succeed in that
And there maybe exceed what Tesla's can do?
Then we'll be in a great place because you know, not every we're not we're never gonna see a road
That's only Tesla's cars are very like
They're very personalized people want there. They're an item of
expression
People want people want like their own looking car. I have an instrument arresting anecdote actually
And you'll have to buy a new car and every year
the cost of buying and open pilot compatible car decreases
Which is really nice like the earliest supported car is the 2016 Civic with touring
So, yeah that it's it's it's definitely nice
One interesting anecdote I have is
so the top-selling top revenue out II dealership in America is
in San Jose or the South Bay area and
I heard a convert overheard a conversation with like manager the dealership recently
Who was saying that they're seeing a complete influx of tesla trade-ins as well as many customers are citing that you know
Like there's too many Tesla's in the South Bay
Like if you ever been this South Bay like you're gonna see more Tesla's there and you do anywhere else on earth
And it's really it's an important anecdote because it like South Bay is basically hit what I call peak Tesla
Like there's there's like a density of like Tesla visible Tesla's on the road and in your office parking lot
at which point like the desire for your
personal desire to buy a Tesla if you don't know any havilland decreases and in fact your desire to keep the Tesla you already have
decreases
because as I said cars are
People want their car to be an item of expression. They don't want it to just look like everyone else's
So that's another point that makes me optimistic
You know about you know, the
You know other cars both of Comus aftermarket level 2 system as well as you know other OAM systems
you know succeeding because
you know look even if Tesla the best auto pilot and like say there was no other company giving us on amia way I
Still doubt, we would not see you know, like everyone convert to Tesla
just based on looks and
Looks and of course, I guess supply alone
So, yeah, look at let's let's make let's let's make sure we can preserve
you know, you know the the diversity of vehicles that people want and
desire and
And then make sure that they can all have, you know cutting it
More options is always good. Yeah
Hey, what's up, we're driving to San Diego Highway five all the way south
In open pallets engaged left lane in at about 74 miles an hour
And it's beautiful it's beautiful
Oh
Yeah, oh
Yeah, it's great
10 San Diego traffic's actually, not bad
We do have a ton of customers in LA. All right. Good luck drew. Thanks. Yeah, I'm gonna get a burrito the moment I land
Where the most people are hanging out in downtown, San Diego
Like for leisure, it's kind of a boogy boogy neighborhood Little Italy
Though there's so many nice things around. We've got 7-eleven on the block. We got a
We got a
desert place right across the street
and
Yeah, I've been commuting in San Francisco like 40 minutes each way to comma which isn't bad because I got Oakland powered, right?
But I have a five-minute walking commute now, which I'm excited for
I'll just now have to deliberately hop in the car and go places to use open toilet. So you
Know got to make sure we're still using our stuff every day
Yeah, we got we got like one of the only offices in downtown San Diego with like two garages
In the front, which is quite nice
Yeah, this the office space for renting has in the past few years been you once everything is in place
Really excited to have like adequate power
Now we had we were running like the power cables for our 3d printers and like servers
That were in our house garage. We were running those cables like - like various bathrooms around the house
It was like a nasty like power setup
But now we have you know, we working with electrician. We got like 240 full outlets for you know our servers now
And so yeah, we got we got we got power to train models and
Obey the Internet's better - we're running on a Comcast residential backup where we have like like
Verizon Wi-Fi connected to our router
So hopefully we don't have to play the internet juggling game
You know the moment the internet down don't internet goes down in the office. Everyone's like hey is the Internet down what's going on?
Don't don't cut us start ups internet that
As a net negative on productivity and you know
Internet's down long enough. Everyone's just gonna fuckin go home
Okay, well I think I'm gonna stop and get some lunch but it's been nice and
Atacama AI archive is gonna upload this video
Probably already streaming it using some bots a huge fan
Thank you for doing that work
And yeah, I'll catch you all later